ANDRÉS DEL CHIARO

Full Stack Developer

https://andres-delchiaro.netlify.app/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/delchiaroa/

anchibro@hotmail.com

Barranquilla, Colombia

PROFILE

Full-stack web developer specialized in React with knowledge in JavaScript, TypeScript, Express, Node and Astro. Fluent level of English and Spanish (mother tongue), and intermediate level in Portuguese. With skills in leadership, teamwork and problem solution. Currently working as a frontend developer in Innomediacreate.

SKILLS

React
JavaScript / TypeScript
TailwindCSS / CSS / HTML
Express / Node
PostgreSQL / MongoDB
Astro

LANGUAGES

Spanish	C2
First Language	
English	C2
Native	
Portuguese	B2

Upper Intermediate

WORK EXPERIENCE

Innomediacreate
Barranquilla, CO

REACT DEVELOPER

10/2023 - NOW

Write and develop functional and well-tested websites with reusable components in React, Shopify and NextJS.

Improve and fix existing websites with clean and reusable code.

Datalog SAS
Bogotá, CO

MUD LOGGER GEOLOGIST

08/2022 - 08/2023

Collect, describe and register rock samples in mud logs for oil and gas wells.

Successfully deliver daily reports with stratigraphic information for the correct development of the wells.

EDUCATION

Universidad de Cataluña Bogotá, CO FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPMENT 03/2023 - 08/2023

Universidad del Norte

B.S IN GEOLOGY 07/2017 - 12/2021

Barranquilla, CO

CERTIFICATIONS

THE ULTIMATE REACT COURSE 2023: REACT, REDUX & MORE Obtained on 10/03/2023

Udemy MASTERING TYPESCRIPT - 2023 EDITION

Obtained on 09/08/2023

Udemy DATA STRUCTURES &

ALGORITHMS

Obtained on 03/01/2023